(Dan)那么，Rato,我们从这节课里学到了什么
(Dan) So, Rato, what have we learned in this lesson?
(Rato)嗯…我学到的是我不想写数据库和ContentProvider
(Rato) Well, I learned that I do not want to write databases and content providers.
你呢
What did you learn in this lesson?
(Dan)嗯... JUnit测试是很棒的
(Dan) Well, JUnit tests are awesome,
还有就是创建应用程序的后台框架是件很光荣的工作
and building the back end framework of our apps is the most glorious of work.
对于创建一个强健的，用户体验很棒的应用来说
It's an absolutely vital part of creating a robust app
这是必不可少的一部分
with a great user experience.
(Rato)我也学到了让Dan说英语口音是很难的事情
(Rato) I also learned that Dan cannot do an English accent.
幸好你可以准备欢迎Katherine在第五课回归
Fortunately, you can get ready to welcome back Katherine for lesson five
那节课上，我们会把activity拆成fragment
where we'll shatter our activity into fragments,
使用content provider来承载更复杂的UI
use our content providers to populate more complex UIs,
还有创建可以像在手机上布局一样好的平板布局
and build layouts that work as well on tablets as they do on phones.
(Dan)就像便利的赛格威进入历史舞台
(Dan) Which seems like a convenient segueway
还有android硬件的进化史一样
into the history and evolution of Android hardware.